hello Jessica from how to ADHD this is
my official invitation to you to come on
the idea cafe come share your experience
on how ADHD affected your college
university life and I will share my
experience of how my neurodiversity
which is ADHD and I also had brain
tumors while under university and with
the change that made to my brain I
experienced University and two very
distinct brain ways I would love to
share that share that story have you
share your story as well as finding one
to two other people to share their
stories live on camera that is what an
idea cafe is it's also a space right now
we run requesting social media
influencers come and share their
influence bring you to the conversation
hopefully some of your subscribers come
along but what I really want is to have
a conversation with you to showcase to
humanity the power of a conversation
when people show up and listen to each
other and hear each other magic can
happen so please come on the idea cafe
let's set up a time that works for us
and we will find other people with
neurodiversity to come share their
experience on how college university was
for them take care